https://www.auditmypc.com/auditmypc/audit-my-pc-privacy-statement

Skip to main content Skip to footerThe owner of this web site is committed to online privacy. The following guidelines pertain to the handling of your information.
Visitors
Visitors may browse the site to learn about our many services, receive company information and find career opportunities without giving any personal information.
Personal Information
Personal information is only made available when a site visitor volunteers it, through our registration or contact page, to request a contact or provide a service.
Information about the Visitor
Web site visitor information with respect to service requests are collected with the use of computer IP addresses on an aggregate basis in which personal information is associated with this data. This data is gathered through the use of Web server log files and where site activity is stored.
Computer Information
Information is used to help prevent abuse, such as audits, diagnose problems with our server, measure the use of our Web site content and to administer our Web site. This information may be used to track down an individual who is attacking or misusing our resources.
Storage of Information
We do store information regarding actions taken by clients when they access their accounts. This information may be provided to employees of our company and to other associates who provide services or products to the client. This information will only be used to research abuse of this free service.
Links at AuditMyPC.com
This site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. This Internet Privacy Statement applies to U.S. clients and Web site visitors only.
Changing the Statement
We may change this privacy statement at any time. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this site.
Questions
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, please feel free to contact us.
Thank you.
FooterMiscellaneous
Free Address Finder
HTML Encoder Decoder
Website Monitoring
Whats My IP Address?
Yes or No
Search this website
